{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Outdoor Kitchen Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46358/":{"taskOID":46358,"originalTaskOID":46358,"setID":1255,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5905,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features would you like for your outdoor kitchen?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20240,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick or Stone Oven","answerDisplayText":"Brick or Stone Oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20241,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20242,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20243,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas Stove","answerDisplayText":"Gas Stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20244,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Island","answerDisplayText":"Island","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20245,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Natural Gas Barbeque","answerDisplayText":"Natural Gas Barbeque","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20246,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pergola","answerDisplayText":"Pergola","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20247,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20248,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sink","answerDisplayText":"Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20249,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Wet Bar","answerDisplayText":"Wet Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5906,"questionDisplayText":"Existing Patio","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you currently have a patio on which to build?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20250,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20251,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5907,"questionDisplayText":"Flooring Selection","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What flooring option would you prefer?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20252,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard","answerDisplayText":"Standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20253,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceramic Tile","answerDisplayText":"Ceramic Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20254,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20255,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5905,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features would you like for your outdoor kitchen?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20240,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick or Stone Oven","answerDisplayText":"Brick or Stone Oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20241,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20242,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20243,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas Stove","answerDisplayText":"Gas Stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20244,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Island","answerDisplayText":"Island","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20245,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Natural Gas Barbeque","answerDisplayText":"Natural Gas Barbeque","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20246,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pergola","answerDisplayText":"Pergola","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20247,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20248,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sink","answerDisplayText":"Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20249,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Wet Bar","answerDisplayText":"Wet Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20240,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick or Stone Oven","answerDisplayText":"Brick or Stone Oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20241,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20242,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20243,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas Stove","answerDisplayText":"Gas Stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20244,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Island","answerDisplayText":"Island","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20245,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Natural Gas Barbeque","answerDisplayText":"Natural Gas Barbeque","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20246,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pergola","answerDisplayText":"Pergola","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20247,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20248,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sink","answerDisplayText":"Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20249,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Wet Bar","answerDisplayText":"Wet Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5906,"questionDisplayText":"Existing Patio","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you currently have a patio on which to build?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20250,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20251,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20250,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20251,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5907,"questionDisplayText":"Flooring Selection","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What flooring option would you prefer?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20252,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard","answerDisplayText":"Standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20253,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceramic Tile","answerDisplayText":"Ceramic Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20254,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20255,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20252,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard","answerDisplayText":"Standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20253,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceramic Tile","answerDisplayText":"Ceramic Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20254,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20255,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/46358/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46358,"taskName":"Outdoor Kitchen-Build","taskDescription":"Build an Outdoor Kitchen","xmTaskDescriptor":"Outdoor Kitchen Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":170,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"outdoor, bbq, entertainment, patio, bar, backyard, island, living, outside,","textMessagingName":"Outdoor_Kitchen_Build","rolloverLongDesc":"Build an Outdoor for entertainment and relaxation.","rolloverShortDesc":"Build an Outdoor for entertainment and relaxation.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find Local Contractors to help design and build your dream Outdoor Kitchen","htmlTitle":"Build an Outdoor Kitchen \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Contractors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":37,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Outdoor Kitchen - Build","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Outdoor Kitchen-Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Outdoor Kitchen Project","urlName":"Outdoor-Kitchen-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Outdoor Kitchen Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"outdoor, bbq, entertainment, patio, bar, backyard","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1255,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}